Finally, Unmute also has a Notetaker.
What we found out is that,
notes that are captured and summarized using your
Claude and Codex harnesses are significantly better
compared to any other Notetaker out there.
And the reason is simple.
You're using the best set of models.
On top of it, you are attaching a really good agentic loop,
a harness which has good context,
and you're not paying for it additionally.
You already pay for your Claude and Codex plan,
so you don't have to pay for any better model for
a particular Notetaker.
So that's really good.
And the good part here, the most important part,
would be that the Unmute Agent
has context about every note that was ever captured on Unmute.
So you can just
invoke Unmute Agent.
You can ask anything about any note and it will bring you,
fetch you the set, the right set of details.
And you can just fire up any task.
You can just ask Unmute Agent that go through
these set of notes and figure out what tasks that I have to work on.
And it'll just create sessions for you like Claude or Codex sessions.
And yeah, that's as simple as that.